[Applause]
Yoshi all
right everybody was
[Applause]
[Music]
fting name is Yoshi oashi Grand Yosi
always appreciate
you 55 or something
whoa holy sh
[Applause]
soal 36 Days yeah what are you doing I
don't really care per se oh my God
that's such a funny joke in
China and that's same drinking cuz uh
Asians shouldn't
drink how
[Music]
the first kidnapping so we we left
around SEC when I was second grade I
think we moved another PARTA Japan wait
you say the first kidnapping well I mean
1980 when when my my parents got
divorced she basically told my dad that
we're moving different part of Osa but
she what she did was she moved myself
and my younger brother to USA so there's
a couple weeks my dad was looking for us
but that's the second time first time
when I was second grade just can you
imagine you you my dad went to work one
morning when he got back work you're
gone all the Furnitures are gone we were
gone oh he was one of those yeah like
emptied the
apartment yeah I didn't know what was
going on you know and uh what were you
told what did your mom tell you I don't
I don't remember only thing I remember
that day we were we were in taxi and the
guy was driving us and we they freaking
around and then we had he parked and my
walked out and walked into this building
wasn't sure if if it's the right
apartment and a guy said and my brother
was way too young something something
something was it this and in Japan this
means like somebody's having Affair or
there's like a secondary person so he
thought is your mom mad because your dad
have an affair or something but this
[ __ ] talking to a second grade
like Jesus yes but this is the 70s
remember like you know back then my dad
would drink bunch of beer while drinking
and driving we were talking about my
cousin we were talking about the time
when I tried to shoot that
um a guy trying to rob us this like 80
1980 80 80 or 81 I can't remember
but were you in La no this is brington
Washington we had a place called uh
handy Conner grocery store 11 Street
bmon Washington which is Navy
town they are the people I live with
first when when I was
um um I don't know technically kidna my
mom kidnapped us and dropped us off in
States and this is the second time she
just took myself and my younger brother
and I think it took my dad like a month
before he figured out that we were
completely out of the
country you know just like uh this
another story just like it took my
Stepmother's family that after I beat
the [ __ ] out of her at my dad's funeral
that they didn't realize I was out of
the country like about 3 weeks month
later cuz they were looking for me you
know thinking I was in Japan or
something soon as I kicked the shed out
of them I I went straight to airport you
know so I know I know the whole
procedure when you assault somebody just
leave you
know believe me that wasn't like the
first time either I've done that kind of
stuff um hang on what it's like a pro
haror attack you
know but you struck multiple times what
are you saying like so you attacked your
aunt no no no no um different things so
the first time like when I was 10 or
11 you know my mother kidnapped us we
were living with
my mother's second oldest sister and she
was with her boyfriend John we called
them Uncle even though they're not
married or anything and um quickly I was
working at the
store cuz even the language is a problem
I could do math so I did Fast
calculation change and stuff you know so
he would just like scan all the stuff
and a guy walked in one time he I think
he was trying to buy something small put
$5 on the counter so I was I did it um
the T and I was ready to get change and
I think my uncle was trying to put it
back all of a sudden he punched my uncle
in the face reach over and tried to grab
cash out of the register you know and
you're yeah and you're you're 10 at this
point 10 or 11 okay and then uh I mean I
didn't even hesitate I grabbed the gun
and and and try tried to shoot the guy
of course I missed and it was so close
it was just kind of embarrassing like
I'm anti- John Wick you know like I I
can't even
hit so my uncle's bleeding and because
the recoil I hit myself in the face I'm
bleeding the guy is scared he doesn't
would he loses
$5 and it it was just it was it's like a
US politic just mess there's no way
the whole thing you know so he just ran
he just ran but um the reason I'm
telling you the story because you
thought it was funny my aunt was mad
because missed the guy you see how crazy
that is like most adults say like thank
God you didn't kill kill the man like
longterm she doesn't give a [ __ ] she
just said like she basically said what
what are you [ __ ] [ __ ] like you
can't even shoot the guy in the face and
she pointed to him going back and forth
like this is how you do it all right
like take that black guy take that black
guy white guy black guy Mex no no Becca
take it black guy Mexican I don't know
why she keeps saying blacks and Mexicans
even though it was a white guy punching
my uncle and there's no mexic in that
area maybe some
blacks but uh six years later when she
had a grow bar down in La she got robbed
by bunch of Mexicans she was like see I
told you maybe that's payback though for
her karma but yeah it was
like my mother's father was a rich man
in
and when he passed away
supposedly his younger brother and
sister took everything left my
grandmother with nothing with like four
daughters and a son maybe five I can't I
don't know how many aunts I have in that
side so I think they became very
desperate and you
know I don't think my aunt was like that
because based on what other people told
but like all the failures and and
trusting people losing money I think it
kind of turned her into kind of hard
person you know right so um but at least
she tried you know and she gave it a red
hot go but well you but but you know
what's funny is like out of all the
women who raised us she probably was the
best person how come because I think she
was fair you know she she makes sure I
went to school make sure I did my
homework my mom did none of that [ __ ]
man I think she was just depressed the
whole time she I don't know
um if I there's a y Mama choke in there
somewhere yeah I think think I think
because she was kind of I'm not saying
they put a gun to her head but I think
she ended up marrying the person she
didn't want to marri and difficult
family
circumstance and she so she she just
like I was saying like that show I did
for you Tuesday where I was being
sincere and hoping to get some empathy
and saying well imagine you know every
morning when my mother see my face it's
a reminder of her unhappiness and I was
expecting a sympathy if the whole
[ __ ] room laugh that I was like oh
okay well I wasn't expecting a laughter
at that spot so people always surpris
you you know first time I saw
pornography my parents are fighting and
U it's really bad cuz my dad my mom
didn't want to Mar my mom she was kind
of for it's like a range maror so she
was very resentful so every time she
used to see my face my face kind of
remind her unhappiness you know
and you know what's so interesting I
didn't expect laughter in that part um
cuz most Americans feel bad for me
but that's a that's a new one okay um I
wasn't trying to be funny but okay um I
think there's there's something there
and I can't I can't express there's
something Swiss there yeah because
because if for her it must be weird
looking at the little Asian kid because
don't they all look the same oh yes yes
no I don't I don't mean that there uh I
mean it is true but go
ahead sometime I can can't even tell my
mother mother of my kids used to call
call a many s she's like these Swiss
Amazons and there's like the the the
mother the matriarch of Swiss families
is something to be studied because you
look at this city like the men are not
men the men are here pretty weak in
terms of their attitude and it's the
it's the women you watch with the kids
and the whole families out who's running
the show there's something there and
it's it's uh yeah and there's also this
thing of um I don't know like like this
City's full of of people that have been
academic
overachievers and there's there's a role
that mothers play there as well so I'm
glad I'm glad you said this because I
think I might be a little wrong to think
everyone that lives in zurk is a
representative the whole country because
if I go out in farms I think you have a
pretty sturdy hearty men who does a hard
[ __ ] different very different people
out there yeah and you know I mean they
were doing all kinds of [ __ ] that's not
PC these days you know yeah yeah for
sure but hold on say so and back in
before like before the kidnapping yeah
what is I mean I call it kidnapping but
I don't I don't know I guess that's
normal in Japan I don't know how that
works buts just [ __ ] off but I mean what
like so you're going to school what what
else do you like how what your daily
life like you doing a paper round are
you are you earning money some how you
sports sports
yeah well when I was living with my dad
what a what a i me just like a dumb kid
wasn't really good in school um had
friends
and oh you know one one thing was
peculiar for sure is
um
um I I'm I'm always the kid who walk
furthest distance away from home like I
don't think most of these parents these
days were allow some kid
just walk
away long distance you know yeah yeah I
think that's kind of gone now like I
don't think that people walk to school
anymore in Japan right
now right it's shocking to me because
reverse culture shock right like I grew
up in Japan but I've been way so long so
when I went back recently there's things
that they do in Japan that is so weird
or like I can't believe it like five or
six year old kids will get on bus and
sub way go someplace really far away by
themselves you could never allow that in
state somebody's going to catch them
murder them you know or do something
Weir but that [ __ ] doesn't happen in
Japan anymore no they they still let
them do that no like but the the the the
murdering [ __ ] oh yeah yeah uh we don't
have that many Americans living in
Japan so but you're living with your dad
for a while what but both my parents
both your parents what's the what's the
day today like like I was saying
sometime I Rend r l take a bus pay I
have enough one um money for bus one way
I don't even know where I'm going so
you're just exploring then I go then I
try to walk back like seven eight n
Miles when I was a kid hell yes yeah so
like I was doing weird [ __ ] like that
and you I remember hearing on she was
saying you you you'd run you were doing
like uber for prostitutes like Uber Eats
or something I mean I was helping some
of my porn friend but that's many years
from that point you know oh okay I
wasn't doing that when I was a kid oh I
know what you're saying you get me
confused because you Uber things new no
no there's there's people in name my
neighborhood they see this dumb kid
which I am and sometimes hey can you do
me something like they told me to go get
go buy them something right so like K
the kid the guy would give me money and
say hey go get me beer back then even
you're underage you could go and and go
to store and buy beers I'm getting it
for my dad or my mom or whatever right
so yeah that's what you have kids for
right
right beer it's going to be some benefit
yeah so so I had people like that in the
neighborhood like you didn't know what
they did but they didn't they didn't
look regular job like my my dad actually
worked for company you know like wear
suit and [ __ ] like that what did he do
work for insurance
company I don't know what I just
remember he worked for insurance company
and boring
job and there's nothing dangerous about
his life you know he was always very
careful with everything he didn't like
the way he grew up with his um dad being
like a laborer so in a really bad
neighborhood so he wanted to climb the
ladder socially somehow I guess did he
uh was he one of those guys that
wouldn't come home at night after work
because they were too shitfaced because
they were drinking with the boss did
that already happen to him I I think
that's like mandatory for a lot of
people working for um in Japanese work
for companies Kisha so when you work for
Kisha that's kind of common thing do you
have to do and so that happened to him
too despite being very especially back
those days when the Japan was recovering
economy was great yeah yeah and but uh
but then then money must have been
flowing in in some sense like he had a
decent
job I never thought we were definitely
not rich my mom's father was a very
wealthy person but when my mother's
father my grandfather passed away he had
a manufacturing company they were rich I
think my dad my mother's father's
siblings took over everything and and
and my grand grandmother ended up with
nothing oh wow and that's why I think
the struggle kind of started from that
point on and I think my mom was was kind
of forced to marry my dad you know yeah
back then you have uh too many I mean I
think my mom had like four or five
sisters and one brother or something
like that so they could they just have
to get start getting rid of the kids you
know couldn't afford that but she
she married the wrong guy you know just
he was a nice guy but just um they were
not compatible you know so that's that's
the thing like whenever I think um my
friends or me things doesn't work about
the opposite sex like it's better that
end and like uh not drag it you know oh
my God yes it's not fun it's not fun but
but it's the other the other side is
horrible like string it out and then
then weird [ __ ] happen so but okay let's
go to the first kidnapping
then so second
grade she says to grab oil Stu we got in
taxi we went to this
apartment within a couple
days I'm going to a different school I
have no idea where the [ __ ] we are and
uh so she could just do that she could
just put you in a different school every
year in Japan um I don't know I forgot
the word but it's something like
Vanishing there's people in Japan under
pressure or they're in a really bad Sons
or they owe money they literally
disappear change their name reappear
someplace else in
Japan the guy who made the show Tokyo
Vice he had a podcast go Vanishing or
something like that talk about that and
Japan is not a large com country and
it's amazing that you could do that but
people do that all the time you know so
for whatever reason they disappeared
that's crazy so it's kind of socially
accepted kind of like I don't know if
it's socially accepting but socially
known to happen you know and uh um yeah
so
I she did she did that and eventually
you know with you and your brother yeah
and I think within a month or two old
son okay you're going to see your father
so we went multiple train up here
someplace else and I see Dad you know
like I didn't know what was going on
like how come Dad we move here what
happened to her dad she she doesn't say
you know Asian parents are all [ __ ]
Liars they never tell you what's going
on you know yeah what was a stupid movie
everything everywhere all the same time
all at once whatever I hate that [ __ ]
movie because couple
things Chinese grandparents are okay
with their grandkids being homosexual
what po of planet do you live in that's
like homosexual Jews in Hollywood think
that's normal you
know do you honestly that's going to be
okay I'll tell you what most likely it's
going to happen the gay grandson
daughter is sleeping in middle of the
night some people walk in the room with
a [ __ ] big wooden Mallet beating the
[ __ ] out of that person or do something
horrendous and at the end of the movie
Asian parents apologizing their Asian
kids yeah there's a limit for SC uh
fantasy and science fiction and there's
a limit to that and that's never going
to happen I was that this is the most
stupidest movie ever you know it's only
Jews and this homosexual make this
fantasy that Asian parents apologize to
their kids this never happened but
there's something about I wish that
movie in a cinema and there was this
it's a it's a great actor whatever I
understand non- Asian people like it but
I was watching like but there's a this
is a fantasy they're not going to poy
their kids I love the fact that that
you're say you're boiling down that
movie to Asian parents never apologize
to their kids and that's the fanty maybe
never hang on because they had a woman
in there with sausage fingers yeah now
it clearly was a fantasy like you know
I've been to places like Hiroshima
Nagasaki I've seen people with sausage
fingers oh [ __ ] so that wasn't really
that unusual to me in fact I saw people
from surviving that I'm old enough to
remember I call them bacon face I called
them okonomiyaki face like a Japanese
pizza face because the residue of the
burn I remember seeing their faces and
of course I'm insens of kid I just
started laughing at their faces holy
[ __ ] but I didn't understand the World
War II and I didn't I thought I thought
they look like that because they did
something bad which clearly they did
because they bombed Pro
harvor you know that French writer uh
Marcel PR am I saying his the name
remembers the things pass of course I
didn't read it because it's such a
massive volumes of books but there was a
couple passages where it's interesting
it's huge books right like so so but I
remember
um something that we had to read in
class where there's
something either it was like a flower or
or cooking or something anyway that main
protagonist smell something and that
trigger certain memories that is very
true when I went back to that
neighborhood grow up certain food
certain smell certain buildings it did
bring a lot of stuff back you know right
so but did did you
remember being there when you oh of
course you you remember being there that
some of the ladies I knew the
neighborhood was clearly hookers looking
back right but you didn't know that at
the time no I remember like one of the
ladies that could you go me something I
did and when I came back she showed me
her tits so that was payment yeah but
see good tids it was really weird when
she did that because if you're young
enough you go a public
bath and so if you went with your dad as
a kid like we have a bath at home but I
think we were having some kind
of problem they're fixing the bathroom
or something so they they took me to
public bath I remember going with my dad
so if you're young enough you you go
because I'm a boy so you go with Dad and
because I'm short soon as I walk in I'm
at the dick level so all this men's dick
you know I'm walking in dicks are coming
at you you like remember in Star Wars
when uh Millennium Falon asteroid the
[ __ ] are coming at me right but if
you're young enough you could go with
your mom and I've seen naked people
ladies right so I've seen naked and and
because I didn't grow up in the west
there was never like Shame about bodies
and stuff okay I'm going to do this were
they all pixeled the dicks still I had
to squint really
hard I could see the
future but so she's so this this woman
shows you his his payments and you're
just like whatever basically you know
what well or you or you went it it was a
little different with that because you
know you know that joke um it's not I
don't know if it's joke but David T
talked about this one time he was
talking about how weird it is when you
go to New York City like a low man like
a really nice Soho and places like that
I don't remember the joke how he said it
but he was funny that um you know
sometime these rich people have a really
pedigree dogs and they have a sweater on
but they only have sweater up here y now
it's weird because now us his dick
sticking out of the dog like you don't
put a sweater on it looks normal but
soon as you put a sweater on it just
looked like it looked like your
grandfather walk around with your dick
sticking out yeah it looks weird
sometime L is it's like emphasized dick
showing the dick part yeah so when she
show me tits that that sent me like oh
instead of going public backing
everybody naked
this made it more special for some
reason but I didn't I couldn't
Pro I couldn't process that idea at all
you know so what did you think when you
saw the tits you were like did you get
horny no I'm I was so young but like but
I was trying to process like this got to
mean mean
something what what what does this
mean you know this got to mean something
it got to mean something yeah that makes
sense you're like what seven and you're
like maybe even younger because okay the
thing I'm going to tell you right now is
one of the the thing I tell beginning
the show that I did in Scotland and uh
um so it was one of like a typical night
they're arguing I'm sleeping all of time
I wake up because they're screaming and
my brother run in tried to stop my
parents from fighting uhhuh and I hate
seen that
[ __ ] I usually put a blanket over my
head just ignore it's not happening but
that particular day I I got so sick of I
went down
downstairs to that room like on the
office and
um my dad had a bunch of books in there
and these are like a really big books
you know and like I don't know why I did
it but I usually pile all this friend
books to pile them up trying to make
like a
castle so I could go and kind of hide so
I piled up and they were just screaming
arguing for so long so I piled it up I
need a couple more books to finish so I
could be inside in Clos and hide and I
ran out of book books and I used all the
books until I noticed on the top shelf
there's a couple books up there so I put
a chair climb up got those books and I
never noticed before that but but these
are special books and and they're
basically nude pictures and people are
engaged in Sex and um and they're not
Asian people they're like Europeans I I
think my dad I don't know it's one of
those fancy Ary sex books you know
basically French something French I
think yeah so I was confused because I
look at them a couple things happened
that was confusing to me
one one of them was magazine rest of the
books one of the magazine you know how
in the 6070 80s porn they put stars in
their genitalia yeah oh yeah yep
okay I thought these white people had
Stars
permanently I thought they were aliens
right cuz I've never seen white people
before
so the young younger listeners it's it
put a start because they're censoring
that but I didn't I thought the
these white I've never seen why people
have stars as dicks yeah so I thought
they're alien because that's why they
have stars whatever right right but the
most bizarre part the part that made me
I think years looking back this was the
first
thing clearly put me in the
path is that they were doing something
that I've never seen before so there
scenes of of course they engage in sex
but I don't know what that was that
that's not the part that interested me
there was a other parts where they were
hugging and kissing each other it's
something I never saw my parents do holy
[ __ ] so I didn't know what this
was so you saw a hog in a book The First
Time In po well I mean Asian people
don't do that in generally speaking no
they don't actually they don't do that
so I didn't I didn't the new thing
didn't bother me cuz I grew up public B
I've seen people naked so I don't have I
didn't grow up like somebody telling me
nudity is bad or right much l sex
because I didn't even know what that was
but this is the first time I saw like I
don't know what this
is but they seem to like each other they
seem to be very
sweet something that my parents don't do
I don't know what this is but this seems
like it's a wonderful thing and we could
use more of this in the world and this
this this what's my introduction to
pornography really this is the first
porn you've ever seen
on your dad's bookshelf and a lady
because because they were fighting and I
need a book to cover and h i and then I
used those to kind of cover the I just
head there you know yeah so
um and of course when you get
older must been that must been when I
was like six or seven years
old and I I it was probably another 3 or
4 years before my mom kidnapped us for
the second and the permanent time where
we went to USA right but so after the
first kidnapping yeah you did go and see
your dad we were allowed to see him
maybe once a month or every other week
or something like that right but you
never moved back in together did you
well um funny you say that cuz I
think maybe little over a year maybe
year and a half there was a knock on the
apartment door and there's my dad and
his best friend and my mom's like [ __ ]
they found us yeah cuz every time we
would see my dad my mom would use
multiple different routes taxi bus and
uh you know secret agent [ __ ] yeah so
and and is your mom has she got a
boyfriend or something
or no I never saw that maybe she did but
I don't know but um but how so was she
living off like while you're in this
other flat okay so in in Osaka um
there's a thing term called Miss mu
showby Mizu is water showby means
business it literally means water
business and the reason why it's called
that cuz uh anybody who works nighttime
whether restaurant or uh performance
artist or maybe even escort they're all
under one category called music Shai and
it's why it's called water business
because a lot of those kinds of
businesses by by uh canal with the light
they have a shimmering like a
otherworldly quality to it oh hence the
water show by you know so my mom was
pouring alcohol in those bars and stuff
and the reason I know that cuz one time
so imagine your second grade your Mom
leaves you middle of the night there's
no babysitter yeah that's how we lived
you know for like second and third grade
and sometime you have to explain
yourself you know but I couldn't believe
doing that to a kid these days like okay
your second grade your brother's barely
kindergarten I'm leaving I'll be back in
the morning or whatever so she did night
shifts at the bar
those working at those Club yeah and
just leaving us you know holy [ __ ] but
she's so I mean she's basically because
your dad's beating her up or something
no no my dad never did that if anything
my my dad will get hit by my mom my
dad's never been a violent guy it's
always my mom hitting my dad okay so but
so she just wanted to get away like so
what why why was he so
repellent he had multiple sister telling
him what to do
and he's not willing to do what uh my
mom was telling him to do maybe he
wasn't successful enough and um
also my mom always remind me that
character from FL Bears Madam baly she
had this fantasy world where she
envisioned living a better life maybe in
entertainment singing cuz she was an
excellent singer and a cook and she
wanted
life better she was a bit artsy I don't
know she's artsy but she like attention
and things like that you know okay and
my dad was
not it well I mean she just that's not
that's not within his personality you
know you work in insurance company
you're a risk averse person you
know so I know for whatever reason it
didn't work out so but then if so in a
way what she's doing is she's escaping a
role she has to play so she's got to
play the role of the mother of the
family she she hat she hated my dad she
hated my dad's family she didn't like
the circumstan although she probably
liked Liv in Japan better than Korea
because Japan was doing economically way
better incredibly well compared to Korea
as an upgrade to them be working in bars
that's like that's kind of economic she
rather work and live on her own than
have this guy that she just didn't want
to be with you know that's inter joke so
I mean that yeah for a fantasy if like
her dream is to be some kind of
performer like this oppression of this I
I don't I don't know because I'm just
trying to understand I'm trying to
understand too but uh these people even
even if you ask my I even if my dad was
alive he just W answer that he just
won't say anything quite you know and
then uh man of a few words I
mean he just he just wasn't very
talkative and uh he doesn't say anything
revealing yeah and my mom even she's
stealing something I don't I don't know
if I should believe that you know so
anyway it's a bad marriage let's go to
the second kidnapping then so the first
kidnapping happened your eventually my
dad found the place found the place she
decided to move back with my
dad and so that's weird and that was
really weird because when we moved back
to the old home did you change school
again of course yeah yeah and how come
comfortable my mom was lying to
neighbors like what were you do hold on
oh I took my kids we went to America my
mom was sick some [ __ ] like I'm so
like that's not true like you know I'm
open my [ __ ] mouth you know but
um so we we were living with my dad but
that didn't last really long because one
night we we summer of
79 we visited our relatives in USA my
grand was was dying and I think winter
was fall of 79 like a couple months
after we return maybe four months it's a
little before
1980 we got a phone call and my mom
started crying I just assumed my
grandmother passed away MH and to me
that
was the beginning of the end cuz I think
when I when we visit the USA for the
first time Sumer 79 I thought okay we're
back living with that things are going
well we're doing vacationing so I
thought things were okay and I was
really really wrong in fact 79 when uh
we were in Hawaii cuz it's a midpoint
between USA Contin us was in Japan and
when we went pro
Harbor and the trip was going well the
whole time I thought oh everything's
taken care of everything's going to be
okay and we're going to live like a
family again and not not realizing we
were basically two three four months
away from receiving phone call where my
mom decided to get divorced
and leave because I I think even for her
she didn't want to get a divorce when
her mom was alive right
so I just remember March 13
1980 um my mom said we're going to get
on the plane you're you're how old 55 no
but how old were you at that um I think
I was 10 years old okay I'm a couple
months away from turning 11 I think
we're going to get on plane we're going
to fly from Osa Japan we're flying to
Tokyo and I was like what why don't we
just take shinan in which is like bullet
train real and then like whatever we got
on playing we woke up next morning we're
back in Hawaii for the second time
because that's when my mom told us um
they're divorced and we we're living in
states there was always a bit of a
disorient feeling with my family and
then the way I grew up I think that's it
feels like semi on purpose in a in a way
it's just like let's not just talk about
[ __ ] let's just did there are some
parents do something weird to prepare
their kids that's not why they did it
they just don't give a [ __ ] yeah they're
smoking cigarette drinking beer think
it's funny you know it's that kind of
[ __ ] yeah that's that's the that's the
environment I grow up you know they're
just yellow trash if there's white trash
there's yellow trash I grow up they're
all yellow trash I'm telling you that's
what I call this episode in a way like
you're there as a for of entertainment
for them they're like I really was a
monkey to to my
momce so it was a lot of that stuff but
I think because of that I think I was
more tolerant of different kinds of
people and different ideas you know
[Music]